{
    "id": "79_Society_97",
    "claim": "In spite of the fact that the students of the archdiocese of Antequera are trying to get rid of Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family, Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg. 'They already have in their ', 'the only owner of this ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', , , , , , ', , ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', , ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', , , , , , , , ', ', ', , ', ', ', ', ', ',. Before the eyes of the elites of the Church and of the re-resentants of the Church, they excavated the mediums of communication that the autorities to which they have resented their complaints have given them reason. There was a demand from the Complainants, where the cars were already closed, since there was no evidence that they were to follow, to affirm. 'These ', ', 'are already in charge of bringing to the Federal and State Police; ', 'it is possible that and ', a Hônesta citizen who has worked my life, ', 'I am forced to believe that if I did some indebid ', said the owner of the ', 'to the ','. Nopemi Velasco said that in the first place the women who try to get rid of her, make an entrance to the force, it was how long she had stopped her life and her family's integrity and that of her family. 'My llama is the signar of the government, Alejandr, Murat Hinojása, by virtue of the fact that the Public Prosecutor's Office has sid misa, that these people have no right ', demands. To his art, Javier Aguay, and Camarg, said that he wanted to get rid of the property improperly, same as he was acquired from legal law, he said that he had. 'The Church's aiderad , noted that and , had caused , , , , , and , chains and candad , and , , , and has the flamboyance of s, , before our statements , ', refer to the ab , , , , of the church which was a s, , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , ,. Aguay-A Camarg-A ex-said that the chains were destroyed by an actuary, who was named a judge who would not give a meeting of the place and so he did?. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "nacionunida.com",
    "date": "24/06/2018",
    "veracity": 0,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "In her family's fact Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family, Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg to Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family, Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg rid of Mr. Velasco Ortiz .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who did nacionunida.com report on 24/06/2018?",
                    "answer": "Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who did Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg get rid of?",
                    "score": 0.6818,
                    "answers": "Mr. Camarg|conj\tMr. Camarg|conj\tthat In her family 's fact Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family , Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg to Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family , Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg rid of Mr. Velasco Ortiz|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Mr. Velasco Ortiz and Mr. Camarg?",
                    "score": 0.6234,
                    "answers": "nacionunida.com reported on 24/06/2018 that In her family 's fact Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family , Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg to Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family , Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg rid of Mr. Velasco Ortiz|ROOT\ton 24/06/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tIn her family 's fact|prep\ther|poss\t's|case\ther family 's fact|pobj\tMr.|compound\tVelasco|compound\tMr. Velasco Ortiz and his family , Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg to Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family , Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg|nsubj\tand|cc\this|poss\t,|punct\tMr.|compound\tJavier|compound\tand|cc\tMr.|compound\tto Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family , Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg|prep\tMr.|compound\tVelasco|compound\tMr. Velasco Ortiz and his family , Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg|pobj\tand|cc\this|poss\t,|punct\tMr.|compound\tJavier|compound\tand|cc\tMr.|compound\tof Mr. Velasco Ortiz|prep\tMr.|compound\tVelasco|compound\tMr. Velasco Ortiz|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "'Mr. Velasco Ortiz already Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family, Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg in her family's 'the only Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family, Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg of this ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', the Church ', ', the Church , ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', 'the Church ', ', ', , , , , , ', , ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', 'the elites of the Church and of the re-resentants of the Church , ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', ', , , , , , , , 'the elites of the Church and of the re-resentants of the Church , ', , ', ', ', ', ', ',.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Mr. Velasco Ortiz and Mr. Camarg?",
                    "score": 0.7044,
                    "answers": "Mr. Velasco Ortiz already Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family , Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg in her family 's ' the only Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family , Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg of this ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , the Church ' , ' , the Church , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' the Church ' , ' , ' , , , , , , ' , , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , '|nmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of Mr. Velasco Ortiz's family?",
                    "score": 0.7027,
                    "answers": "Mr.|compound\tMr.|compound\this|poss\this family , Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg|conj\tMr.|compound\tJavier|compound\tMr.|compound\t's|case\tMr.|compound\t' the only Mr. Velasco Ortiz and his family , Mr. Javier Aguay and Mr. Camarg of this|appos\this|poss\this family|conj\tMr.|compound\tJavier|compound\tMr.|compound\tof this|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Mr. Velasco Ortiz married to?",
                    "score": 0.6856,
                    "answers": "' the Church ' , ' , ' , , , , , , ' , , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , ' , '|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Before the eyes of the the elites of the Church and of the re-resentants of the Church of the Church and of the a Hônesta citizen who has worked my life of the Church, they a Hônesta citizen who has worked my life the mediums of communication that the autorities to which they have resented their complaints have given them reason.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who has given the Hônesta citizen reason to complain?",
                    "answer": "autorities to which they have resented their complaints"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many Hônesta citizens have worked for the Church of the Church?",
                    "score": 0.614,
                    "answers": "nacionunida.com reported on 24/06/2018 that Before the eyes of the the elites of the Church and of the re - resentants of the Church of the Church and , they a Hônesta citizen who has worked my life the mediums of communication that the autorities to which they have resented their complaints have given them of the a Hônesta citizen who has worked my life of the Church reason|ROOT\ton 24/06/2018|prep\tthe a Hônesta citizen who has worked my life of the Church|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the names of the Hônesta citizen who worked for the Church?",
                    "score": 0.5363,
                    "answers": "of the a Hônesta citizen who has worked my life of the Church|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the autorities to which they have resented their complaints?",
                    "score": 0.5195,
                    "answers": "their|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the means of communication that the autorities use for their complaints?",
                    "score": 0.4872,
                    "answers": "communication|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of communication?",
                    "score": 0.4868,
                    "answers": "the mediums of communication|dobj\tof communication|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "There was a demand from the Complainants, where the cars were already Nopemi Velasco , since there was no evidence that they Nopemi Velasco to follow, to affirm.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the car that the Complainants wanted to follow?",
                    "answer": "Nopemi Velasco"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the demand for the cars from the Complainants?",
                    "score": 0.6472,
                    "answers": "on 24/06/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tThere|expl\ta|det\tthe|det\t,|punct\twhere|advmod\tthe|det\tthe cars|nsubj\talready|advmod\tNopemi Velasco|attr\t,|punct\tsince|mark\tthere|expl\tno|det\tthat|mark\tthey Nopemi Velasco|nsubj\tNopemi Velasco|appos\tto|aux\t,|punct\tto|aux\tto affirm|dep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "'These ', ', 'are already in Nopemi Velasco of bringing to the Federal and State Police; ', 'it is possible that and ', a Hônesta citizen who has worked my life, ', 'I am forced to believe that if I did some indebid ', said the owner of the ', 'to the ','.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the owner of the ', 'to the ', say about the Hônesta citizen?",
                    "answer": "'I am forced to believe that if I did some indebid"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the Hônesta citizen say to the police?",
                    "score": 0.5674,
                    "answers": "that if I did some indebid ' , said the owner of the ' , ' to the ' ,|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the owner of the Hônesta citizen who worked for the Federal and State Police?",
                    "score": 0.5501,
                    "answers": "' , said the owner of the ' , '|parataxis\tof the|prep\tthe '|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Nopemi Velasco and the police?",
                    "score": 0.4625,
                    "answers": "' These ' , ' , ' are already in Nopemi Velasco of bringing to the Federal and State Police ;|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Nopemi Velasco said that in the first place the women who try to get rid of her, make an entrance to the force, it was how long she had stopped her life and her family's integrity and that of her family.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that in the first place the women who try to get rid of her, make an entrance to the force, it was how long she had stopped her life and her family's integrity and that of her family's integrity?",
                    "answer": "Nopemi Velasco"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Nopemi Velasco and the women who tried to get rid of her?",
                    "score": 0.3986,
                    "answers": "nacionunida.com reported on 24/06/2018 that Nopemi Velasco said that in the first place the women who try to get rid of her , make an entrance to the force , it was how long she had stopped her life and her family 's integrity and that of her family|ROOT\tthat|mark\tNopemi|compound\tthat Nopemi Velasco said that in the first place the women who try to get rid of her , make an entrance to the force , it was how long she had stopped her life and her family 's integrity and that of her family|ccomp\tthat|mark\tin the first place the women who try to get rid of her , make an entrance to the force|prep\tthe|det\tthe first place the women who try to get rid of her , make an entrance to the force|pobj\tthe|det\tthe women who try to get rid of her ,|nsubj\twho|nsubj\twho try to get rid of her|relcl\tto|aux\tget|auxpass\tof her|prep\ther|pobj\t,|punct\tthe women who try to get rid of her , make an entrance to the force|relcl\tan|det\tto the force|prep\tthe|det\tthe force|pobj\t,|punct\tit|nsubj\tthat in the first place the women who try to get rid of her , make an entrance to the force , it was how long she had stopped her life and her family 's integrity and that of her family|ccomp\thow|advmod\thow long|advmod\tshe|nsubj\thad|aux\thow long she had stopped her life and her family 's integrity and that of her family|ccomp\ther|poss\tand|cc\ther|poss\t's|case\tand|cc\tof her family|prep\ther|poss\ther family|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "'My llama is the signar of the government, Alejandr, Murat Hinojása, by virtue of the fact that the Public Prosecutor's Office has sid misa, that these people have no right ', demands.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did nacionunida.com report that the people of Alejandr, Murat Hinojása have?",
                    "answer": "no right"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the Public Prosecutor's Office say about My llama being the signar of the government?",
                    "score": 0.6561,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t'|punct\tthe|det\tthe|det\t,|punct\t,|punct\t,|punct\tby virtue of the fact that the Public Prosecutor 's Office has sid misa , that these people have no right|prep\tof the fact that the Public Prosecutor 's Office has sid misa , that these people have no right|prep\tthe|det\tthe fact that the Public Prosecutor 's Office has sid misa , that these people have no right|pobj\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tPublic|compound\thas|aux\tmisa|dep\t,|punct\tthat|mark\tthese|det\tthese people|nsubj\tthat the Public Prosecutor 's Office has sid misa , that these people have no right|acl\tno|det\tno right|dobj\t'|punct\t,|punct\tdemands|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "To his art, Javier Aguay, and Camarg, said that he wanted to get rid of the property improperly, same as he was acquired from legal law, he said that he had.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 24/06/2018 that Javier Aguay wanted to get rid of his property improperly?",
                    "answer": "nacionunida.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did Javier Aguay want to get rid of his property?",
                    "score": 0.7557,
                    "answers": "nacionunida.com reported on 24/06/2018 that To his art , Javier Aguay , and Camarg , said that he wanted to get rid of the property improperly , same as he was acquired from legal law , he said that he had|ROOT\ton 24/06/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tTo his art|prep\this|poss\this art|pobj\t,|punct\tJavier|compound\t,|punct\tand|cc\t,|punct\tthat|mark\the|nsubj\tthat he wanted to get rid of the property improperly|ccomp\tto|aux\tget|auxpass\tto get rid of the property improperly|xcomp\tof the property|prep\tthe|det\tthe property|pobj\timproperly|advmod\t,|punct\tsame|advmod\tas|mark\the|nsubjpass\twas|auxpass\tsame as he was acquired from legal law|advcl\tfrom legal law|prep\tlegal|amod\tlegal law|pobj\t,|punct\the|nsubj\tthat|mark\the|nsubj\tthat he had|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Javier Aguay and Camarg say about getting rid of the property?",
                    "score": 0.6374,
                    "answers": ", Javier Aguay , and Camarg , said that he wanted to get rid of the property improperly|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Javier Aguay and Camarg?",
                    "score": 0.5208,
                    "answers": "Javier Aguay , and Camarg ,|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "'The Church's aiderad , noted that and , had caused , , , , , and , chains and candad , and , , , and has the flamboyance of s, , before our statements , ', refer to the ab , , , , of the church which was a s, , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , ,.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What has the flamboyance of the church caused?",
                    "score": 0.6392,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t'|punct\t's|case\tthat|prep\thad caused , , , , , and , chains and candad , and , ,|conj\tchains and candad , and , ,|conj\tcandad|conj\tour statements|pobj\t'|punct\ta|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the church's flamboyance?",
                    "score": 0.6171,
                    "answers": "of the church which was a s , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , ,|prep\tthe church which was a s , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , ,|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the church's aiderad?",
                    "score": 0.5968,
                    "answers": "the ab , , , , of the church which was a s , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , ,|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the Church's aiderad?",
                    "score": 0.5947,
                    "answers": "The Church 's aiderad|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the church and the flamboyance?",
                    "score": 0.5902,
                    "answers": "' , refer to the ab , , , , of the church which was a s , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , ,|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Aguay-A Camarg-A ex-said that the chains were destroyed by an actuary, who was named a judge who would not give a meeting of the place and so he did?.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the actuary who destroyed the chains?",
                    "answer": "a judge who would not give a meeting of the place"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Did Aguay-A Camarg-A ex-said that the chains were destroyed by an actuary?",
                    "score": 0.7182,
                    "answers": "on 24/06/2018|prep\tAguay|compound\tCamarg|compound\tAguay - A Camarg - A|nsubj\tthat Aguay - A Camarg - A ex|ccomp\twho was named a judge who would not give a meeting of the place and so he did|relcl\ta judge who would not give a meeting of the place and so he did|oprd\tso he did|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who destroyed the chains of Aguay-A Camarg-A?",
                    "score": 0.62,
                    "answers": "said that the chains were destroyed by an actuary , who was named a judge who would not give a meeting of the place and so he did|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Aguay-A Camarg-A say about the actuary who destroyed the chains?",
                    "score": 0.5928,
                    "answers": "nacionunida.com reported on 24/06/2018 that Aguay - A Camarg - A ex - said that the chains were destroyed by an actuary , who was named a judge who would not give a meeting of the place and so he did ?|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did an actuary say about Aguay-A Camarg-A ex-said?",
                    "score": 0.5327,
                    "answers": "by an actuary , who was named a judge who would not give a meeting of the place and so he did|agent"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}